It stuckled to my teeth
它粘到我牙上了
This is so delicious, thank you
这很好吃，谢谢
I am here to filter yeah everything
我是来过滤一切的
That's exactly why I'm learning it
这正是因为我还在学着管住自己的嘴
Before he says it I have that ability
在他说之前我有这种能力
So I can just go like that
所以我可以像这样
I don't give anyone the scripts
我没有给任何人剧本
I did read the scripts
我读过
Did you
真的？
Yes because I give you the script
是的因为我和你可不一样
Don't walk off, come back, come back
别走，回来，回来
I did I did I did my outlook
我构建了我自己的世界观
I'm old school
在我高中的时候
And I've also kept state secrets of us
同时我也保守了这个秘密
That's how I check it to be die die so shortly
这就是我检验其角色性死亡的方式
You'll find out it does
很快你就会发现的确如此
Well it does have
哦这确实有…
Ah, spoilers
防剧透！
In Infinity War are you a freelancer
在无限战争中你是自由职业者吗？
I mean do you go back to the Avengers
我的意思是你是否回到了复仇者联盟
And that's a good question
哦这是一个很好的问题
I'll answer it, emm he is...
我来回答这个问题，额他是...
I'm very stressed right now
我现在非常紧张
Cause this is live so I am really trying ...
因为这是现场直播，我在尝试着…
so I am trying to sit with them and these guys do a talking
所以我一直想和他坐在一起接受采访
I have a big hands, so in the moment
在这种时候，我能用我的大手
Who do you think guys will be the worst at this game
你们觉得谁在这场比赛中会表现的最差劲？
Why not been there that day?
你那天为什么不去
oh I can't do by this
我不能说这个
Moving on! moving on!
继续！继续
We will gain all the spoilers and everything we need
我们将看到所有的剧透和我们想知道的一切
That's why we have been DC
这就是为什么我们来到了这儿
Whenever I
当...
BI---
哔--
Ah, lots of stake in it, and a little bit nuts
额，有许多条状物在里头，还有一些坚果
It stuck on my...
它粘在我...
What do you do
你在干嘛？
It's stuck on my lip
它粘在了我的嘴唇上
It wont go on... Help me
它掉不下去了…救救我
How are you going my friend?
兄弟怎么样？
It’s tasty
这也太好吃了叭
Hello the Benjamin
你好本杰明
How are you Karl
你好啊卡尔
Hey baby it's nothing good in there
能在这儿太好啦
Is that my juice
这是我的果汁吗
Bring Tom this juice I bought you
把我给你的果汁给汤姆
It gets you pretty when you doesn't have a show girl
宝贝，多喝果汁能让你在不上节目的时候依旧英俊可人
Are there new characters in our movie?
电影里会出现新角色吗？
All that new character in this movie
新的角色在电影里...
We had to catch them all when it's gonna make a parent?
涉及剧透的问题
How working with Robert was?
你觉得和罗伯特一起工作怎么样？
It was actually him
真的是他
Yeah right
对的
He never facetime with me
我从没和他视频聊天过
This is so weird
这好奇怪
Hey man, how do you doing
嘿，你在干嘛呢？
Are you doing a good job?
你现在干的咋样
I'm doing a good job
我觉得我做的不错
Yeah I'm think so
是的，也许吧
Please ask that reporter to here the phone
让记者听一下电话吧
Okay he would like to speak to you
好的，他想和你说话
It's Robin
这是罗宾斯
He's being perfect actually he's representing you guys very well
他很完美，实际上他代表了你
It's been it's been great
他做的很不错
Ivan will glossies to try look at she's very body jay right
伊万会滑冰，你看他健美的身材
It's right it's very good
对，这很好杰伊
You really are taking cues from master
你真的从他那儿获得启发了
The reason being is because we Peter Parker and
原因是因为我们Peter Parker和...
Spoilers!
防剧透！
Sorry no
对不起
It's not as I bet
这不像我打赌的那样
It's not why are you answering your phone in the middle of an interview
这不是..为什么你在采访中途接电话？
Because it's you
因为是你的电话啊
If it my mom I will ummemm
如果是我妈我就把电话摁掉了
But it's Robert Downey Jr. yeah I'll see what's happening
但如果是你，我会想知道发生了什么
You know the rules
你知道规则的
Follow me
跟着我
Yes I mean so
是的，我是说
We do not know the rules
我们遵循这里的规则，但我们并不完全知道规则
And it's always scary when somebody says you know the rules
这总是很恐怖当别人说你知道规则的时候
Yeah man you can keep dancing
是的，你只要继续跳舞就行
I'll figure this out
我会弄清楚这个的
That's a surgery but you are younger
是个小手术，你很年轻
So you'll heal fast
所以你会很快康复的
It's not you in it man
又不是你在这儿
Do you think I should push the red button
你觉得我要按这个红色的按钮吗
Yeah I think you should
是的，我觉得你应该按下去
What's this dude press to operate
这个按下操作是什么？
No! Don’t touch it
别碰它！
Did you push it
你按下去了吗
I didn't push it
我没有
Congratulations you have solved your puzzles. You are free to go
恭喜！你们完成了挑战，可以安全离开了
That's why I'm here just the police him
这就是为什么我在这里，我在这里只是监督他
And It don't need me and spider man
这不需要我和蜘蛛侠一起
It's I'm just here to go like this
我就只是在这儿像这样
Who will you think the least trustworthy when it comes to the secrets
保守秘密的时候，你们之中谁是最不值得信赖的？
No spoilers
差点剧透了
Yeah like the menu the wind blew and the menu flew out
是的，就像菜单一样，风一吹，菜单就飞了
He was just like yeah and he caught the menu
他就像是...他抓住了菜单
Yeah it was crazy perfectly I also wasn't cool about it either
是啊，这太疯狂了，我也不喜欢
I didn't like catch it and put it down
我不喜欢抓住它，然后放下它
Did you see that
你看到了吗？
Do you all survive in the film
你们饰演的角色在电影的最后都活着吗？
Are there characters that that don't make it
有没有那些不能让它出现的角色？
Don’t say anything!
别说话！
Moving on
继续
You actually just got a little nervous didn't you
你有点紧张，是不是？
I did I'm really sressed
我确实很有压力
这里给友友们
种草一些蜘蛛侠周边